

GAME ENGINE & GAMEPLAY

DEVELOPER

## **Details**

Barcelona
Spain
+34 671 11 62 23
magalenyo7@gmail.com

#### Links

LinkedIn

Github (@magalenyo)

Website

Shutdown (video game)

Boundead (video game)

#### **Skills**

Java, C++, C#, Angular

SVN and Git (Github and BitBucket)

Continuos integration with Jenkins

Project development

OpenGL, GLSL

# Languages

Spanish (Native)

Catalan (Native)

English (Fluent - B2 Certificate)

### **Profile**

I'm a 25 years old passionate programmer, currently working as a Full Stack developer for NTT DATA Europe & Latam.

Interested in software development, but specially in Game Engine programming and Games development. I'm also interested in Graphics, VFX and 3D Modelling.

# **Employment History**

### Solutions Analyst, NTT Data Europe & Latam, Barcelona

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

Working with Agile methodologies like Scrum (+Kanban and Jira), and SVN and Git (Github) in the following projects:

- Development of Allianz Insurance websites and internal tools.
  - Programming: full stack development of an insurance policy contract site and the development of an internal UI Editor tool to create Workflows.
     Both projects were developed in Angular and Java Springboot.
- Development and maintenance of Zurich Insurance customers' web portal.
  - Projects development: task estimation, team organization, creation of technical and functional documents, creation of requirements documents.
  - Programming: full stack development of the client's site with a custom framework based on Java, HTML, CSS and JS.

#### Programmer, EUTI Software, Girona

FEBRUARY 2019 - JUNE 2019

Development and publishing of an application for Android and iOS made with Xamarin.Forms (C#) and maintenance of a server made in Visual Basic.

### Education

# Master's Degree in Advanced Programming for AAA Video Games, Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya (UPC), Barcelona

OCTOBER 2020 - NOVEMBER 2021

- Development of a 3D game engine programmed in C++ and OpenGL. Check the engine repository here:
  - Graphics: UI Shaders, Dissolve Shader (Simplex Noise Map), Chromatic aberration, MSAA integration.
  - Navigation Module: integration of Recast & Detour for the creation of NavMesh, NavAgent and NavObstacle.
- Development of a 3D videogame in C++. Take a look at the <u>game trailer</u> or the full gameplay <u>here</u>. Check the videogame repository <u>here</u>.
  - Gameplay: Final Boss fully customizable Bullet Hell, scripting for simple behaviors, scripting for UI animations.

### B.S. in Computer Engineering, Universitat de Girona (UDG), Girona

SEPTEMBER 2014 - JULY 2019

Specialized in Software Engineering.

**Boundead:** as a final project, a colleague and I developed a 2.5D action/platform video game made in Unity (C#).

To check the gameplay, access the  $\underline{\text{Youtube Playlist}}$  and check the source code  $\underline{\text{here}}$ . To play it yourself,  $\underline{\text{download the project}}$ .